{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"they lend credibility to your documentation.",
					"rapid facial swelling might mask hidden injuries.",
					"hospital staff require frequent patient updates.",
					"such injuries can affect the respiratory system."
				],
				"question": "Frequent reassessments of the patient with face or neck injuries are most important because:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "such injuries can affect the respiratory system."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"of the risk for airway problems.",
					"the spine might be injured as well.",
					"swelling might mask hidden injuries.",
					"bleeding must be controlled early."
				],
				"question": "Facial injuries should be identified and treated as soon as possible because:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "of the risk for airway problems."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"1 inch posterior to the external opening of the ear.",
					"1 inch posterior to the angle of the mandible.",
					"1 inch inferior to the external opening of the ear.",
					"½ inch anterior to the external opening of the ear."
				],
				"question": "The mastoid process is located approximately:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "1 inch posterior to the external opening of the ear."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"mandible.",
					"zygoma.",
					"mastoid.",
					"maxillae."
				],
				"question": "The upper jawbones are called the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "maxillae."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Allows flexion of the neck",
					"Connects the scapulae together",
					"Provides respiration",
					"Allows movement of the head"
				],
				"question": "What is the function of the sternocleidomastoid muscle?",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "Allows movement of the head"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Briskly constricting pupils when exposed to light",
					"Failure of the eyes to follow movement of an object",
					"One pupil larger in size than the other pupil",
					"Failure of the eyes to move in the same direction"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following findings would be least suggestive of a head injury?",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care for Specific Injuries"
			},
			"back": "Briskly constricting pupils when exposed to light"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"mandible.",
					"maxillae.",
					"mastoid.",
					"zygoma."
				],
				"question": "The lower jawbone is called the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "mandible."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"are well protected by the maxillae and mandible.",
					"contain a relatively small number of nerve fibers.",
					"have a rich blood supply and bleed profusely.",
					"swell minimally when exposed to blunt trauma."
				],
				"question": "The skin and underlying tissues of the face:",
				"source": "See Injuries of the Face and Neck"
			},
			"back": "have a rich blood supply and bleed profusely."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"below the thyroid cartilage and forms the upper part of the trachea.",
					"the small indentation in between the thyroid and cricoid cartilages.",
					"the lower part of the larynx that is formed by the cricoid cartilage.",
					"the upper part of the larynx that is formed by the thyroid cartilage."
				],
				"question": "The Adam’s apple is:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "the upper part of the larynx that is formed by the thyroid cartilage."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"lacrimal gland.",
					"corneal duct.",
					"posterior orbit.",
					"optic chiasma."
				],
				"question": "The conjunctiva are kept moist by fluid produced by the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "lacrimal gland."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"compression of one or both optic nerves.",
					"blood in the anterior chamber of the eye.",
					"an acute rupture of the globe of the eye.",
					"inflammation of the iris, cornea, and lens."
				],
				"question": "The term “hyphema” is defined as:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care for Specific Injuries"
			},
			"back": "blood in the anterior chamber of the eye."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"at the angle of the jaw.",
					"slightly above the ear.",
					"just anterior to the tragus.",
					"over the mastoid process."
				],
				"question": "The superficial temporal artery can be palpated:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "just anterior to the tragus."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"it should become smaller in size.",
					"the opposite pupil should dilate.",
					"both pupils should dilate together.",
					"it should become larger in size."
				],
				"question": "When a light is shone into the pupil:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "it should become smaller in size."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"most patients with facial trauma will need surgery.",
					"they might need to call a specialist to see the patient.",
					"it saves time on repeat assessments at the hospital.",
					"they must make arrangements for an ICU bed."
				],
				"question": "When transporting a patient with a facial injury, it is most important to be as descriptive as possible with the hospital regarding the patient’s injuries because:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "they might need to call a specialist to see the patient."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"iris.",
					"retina.",
					"cornea.",
					"sclera."
				],
				"question": "The white portion of the eye is called the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "sclera."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"digital pressure to an adjacent pulse point.",
					"direct pressure using dry, sterile dressings.",
					"pressure dressings and chemical ice packs.",
					"ice packs and elevation of the patient’s head."
				],
				"question": "Bleeding from soft-tissue injuries to the face is most effectively controlled with:",
				"source": "See Emergency Medical Care"
			},
			"back": "direct pressure using dry, sterile dressings."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"pinna.",
					"stapes.",
					"tragus.",
					"incus."
				],
				"question": "The small, rounded, fleshy bulge immediately anterior to the ear canal is called the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "tragus."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"cornea.",
					"sclera.",
					"retina.",
					"conjunctiva."
				],
				"question": "The inner surface of the eyelids and the exposed surface of the eye itself are covered by a delicate membrane called the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "conjunctiva."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is easier to see and palpate than the thyroid cartilage.",
					"is the only complete circular cartilage of the trachea.",
					"lies superior to the thyroid cartilage in the neck.",
					"lies superior to the cricothyroid membrane in the neck."
				],
				"question": "The cricoid cartilage:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "is the only complete circular cartilage of the trachea."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-28-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"globe.",
					"cornea.",
					"orbit.",
					"sclera."
				],
				"question": "The eyeball itself is referred to as the:",
				"source": "See Anatomy and Physiology"
			},
			"back": "globe."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-28",
		"label": "Chapter 28"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}